sookachat.com 2011-11-02

# Privacy Policy - SookaChat - Community Chat

SookaChat’s Customer Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by SookaChat anytime you interact with SookaChat, such as when you visit our website, when you subscribe to SookaChat's products and services, or when you contact our sales or support associates.

Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at SookaChat, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

### Why we collect personal information

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

### What information we collect and how we may use it

We may use personal information to provide products that you have requested as well as for auditing, research, and analysis to improve SookaChat’s products.

  * When you interact with SookaChat, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences; your credit card information and information about the SookaChat products you own, purchase transaction reference number and date of purchase; and information relating to a support or service issue.
  * We may ask for your personal information when you’re requesting support or service over the phone, downloading a software update, registering your products, or purchasing a product.
  * There are a number of situations in which your personal information may help us give you better products. For example:

### Publicly displayed information is public

For example, if you choose to make information, which was previously non-public, available by enabling certain user features, SookaChat will collect that information from your interaction and the information will become publicly available.If you use support forum or community site on SookaChat website you should be aware that any information you share is visible to other users. Personally identifiable information you submit to one of these forums can be read, collected, or used by other individuals to send you unsolicited messages. SookaChat is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

For example, if you choose to make information, which was previously non-public, available by enabling certain user features, SookaChat will collect that information from your interaction and the information will become publicly available.

### When we disclose your information

SookaChat takes your privacy very seriously. SookaChat does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers.

#### Within our company - Slashes & Dots Sdn. Bhd.

To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with legal entities within our company globally who will take steps to safeguard it in accordance with SookaChat’s privacy policy.

#### With our service providers, vendors, and strategic partners.

At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.There are also times when it may be advantageous for SookaChat to make certain personal information about you available to companies that SookaChat has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for SookaChat to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with SookaChat’s policies, except if we inform you otherwise at the time of collection.

At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.

### How we protect your personal information

SookaChat takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers.

#### Cookies and other technologies

As is standard practice on many corporate websites, SookaChat’s website uses “cookies” and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our website, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. And we use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. SookaChat will not use the information collected to market directly to that person.

In some of our email messages we use a "click-through URL" linked to content on the SookaChat website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. We track this click-trhough data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our custoemr communications. If you prefer not to be tracked simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the email.

#### Our commitment to your privacy

As we said, SookaChat takes protecting your privacy very seriously. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to SookaChat employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company. In addition, SookaChat supports industry initiatives to preserve privacy rights on the Internet and in all aspects of electronic commerce.
